Arlene Blum papers, M1558
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives
- Series 3: Accession 2010-021
  - "Tents in the Clouds, The First Women's Himalayan Expidition" - Monica Jackson and Elizabeth Stark, Foreword by Arlene Blum; published paperback copy of book (Box 60, Item 3)
  - "The Boldest Dream, The story of twelve who climed Mount Everest" - Rick Ridgeway; published hardback copy of book; Arlene part of team (Box 60, Item 4)
  - "Women on High, Pioneers of Mountaineering" - Rebecca A. Brown, Foreward by Arlene Blum; published hardback copy of book (Box 60, Item 5)
  - "Desert, Mountain, Sea" - Sue Leather; published paperback copy of book; includes adaptation from "Annapurna: A Women's Place" by Arlene Blum (Box 60, Item 6)
  - "Rocks and Roses" - Edited by Mikel Vause; published paperback copy of book; includes "The Tragic Mountain" by Arlene Blum (Box 60, Item 7)
  - "On Top of the World, Five Women Explorers in Tibet" - Luree Miller, Foreward by Arlene Blum; published paperback copy of book (Box 60, Item 8)
  - "MoveOn's 50 Ways to Love Your Country"; published paperback copy of book; includes essay by Annalise Blum (Box 60, Item 9)
  - "Breaking Trail, A Climbing Life" - complete book draft [2 folders] (Box 61, Folders 1-2)
  - "Breaking Trail, A Climbers Life" - book image samples (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - "Annapurna: A Women's Place" - screenplay by Marvin A. Gulk (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - "Annapurna" - production manual & movie pitch correspondence (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - "Annapurna" - film correspondence (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Climbing notes & correspondence - Annapurna (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - GHT Diaries, (1981-1982) [4 folders] (Box 62, Folders 1-4)
  - GHT proposals & drafts; includes book proposals for "The Great Himalayan Traverse"; "A Walk Across the Great Himalayan Range" drafts for Smithonian Magazine article; published version of GHT article in Smithonian Magazine [8 folders] (Box 63, Folders 1-8)
  - Annapurna book material; includes publishing and distribution correspondence, book reprints, film agreement and correspondence [10 folders] (Box 64, Folders 1-10)
  - Annapurna miscellaneous material; includes expidition info, book drafts, book publicity and news articles; 3.5" diskettes (Annapurna documents) [16 folders] (Box 65, Folders 1-16)
  - Vera Watson/Alison Chadwick-Onyszkiewicz (VWACO) Memorial Fund; includes grant applications, contribution info., committee meetings, press releases, contact lists, correspondence [7 folders] (Box 66, Folders 1-7)
  - "Women in High Places: A History of Women in Mountaineering"; includes book proposal, collaboration agreement, drafts, notes, correspondence [9 folders] (Box 67, Folders 1-9)
  - "Women in High Places: A History of Women in Mountaineering" book research; personal profiles of women mountaineers, historical research of women in mountaineering; includes publications, news articles, correspondence, notes [29 folders] (Carton 68, Folders 1-29)
  - "Women in High Places: A History of Women in Mountaineering" additional book research; includes publications, news articles, correspondence, notes [13 folders] (Box 69, Folders 1-13)
  - Himalayan Trekking Course material; includes coursebooks, course lists, language information, publicity and advertising, research, correspodence, notes [43 folders] (Carton 70, Folders 1-43)
  - Arlene's published articles; includes published copies of articles, drafts, correspondence [23 folders] (Box 71, Folders 1-23)
  - Miscellaneous writing material; includes article inquiries and proposals, drafts of potential articles, research, correspondence, articles written about Arlene [19 folders] (Box 72, Folders 1-19)
  - Various Treks; Great Himalayan Treks, Alexandria David-Neel Expedition, other treks around the world; includes travel plans, member lists, equipment lists, permits, funding, trek publicity, news articles, correspondence [63 folders] (Carton 73, Folders 1-63)
  - Miscellaneous Travel & Advetures; Great Barrier Reef, diving, ski touring, caving, running; includes travel pamphlets, news articles, correspondence [15 folders] (Box 74, Folders 1-15)
  - Arlene's undergraduate material; includes course files, notes, research [10 folders] (Box 75, Folders 1-10)
  - Arlene's postdoctoral material; includes Arlene's Ph. D thesis and other published papers, postdoctoral position openings and research, science and the environment lectures and research [15 folders] (Box 76, Folders 1-15)
  - Carcinogen research files; includes papers, notes, news articles, correspondence [8 folders] (Box 77, Folders 1-8)
  - Chemical & cancer research material; includes diet and cancer relationship, publications, news articles, correspondence [11 folders] (Box 78, Folders 1-11)
  - Volcano research files; includes publications, papers, notes, data, correspondence [8 folders] (Box 79, Folders 1-8)
  - Himalayan Fair; includes event planning, vendor info., event fliers/posters, event maps, publicity, meeting notes, correspondence; also includes Oxfam America Worldfest [10 folders] (Box 80, Folders 1-10)
  - Honors/Awards; includes recognition of Arlene for various honors and awards [5 folders] (Box 81, Folders 1-5)
  - Miscellaneous news articles and publications; includes articles about Arlene, women expolerers and climbers, Himalayan treks, other various material on mountaineering and women [37 folders] (Carton 82, Folders 1-37)
  - Miscellaneous material; includes expert witness request, correspondence, family & health studies, religion info. [22 folders] (Box 83, Folders 1-22)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence [12 folders] (Box 84, Folders 1-12)
  - Annapurna book photographs (101-135)[1 folder] (Flat-box 85, Folder 1)
  - Annapurna book photographs (136-171)[1 folder] (Flat-box 86, Folder 1)
  - Annapurna book photographs (172-197)[1folder] (Flat-box 87, Folder 1)
  - Annapurna book photographs (198-212) & (A1-A9)[2 folders] (Flat-box 88, Folder 1-2)
  - Annapurna book photographs (extras)[2 folders] (Flat-box 89, Folder 1-2)
  - Annapurna book photographs (original proofs returned from Random House, Inc.); includes digital photos (compact disc), photo proofs, maps, coprrespndence [4 folders] (Flat-box 90, Folder 1-4)
  - Annapurna & Great Himalayan Traverse diaries [24 audio cassette tapes] (Flat-box 91, Items 24)
  - Everest & Bhrigupanty interviews of team members [25 audio cassette tapes] (Flat-box 92, Items 25)
  - Himalayan Trekking Course [20 audio cassette tapes] (Flat-box 93, Items 20)
- Series 4: Slides (from accession 2010-021)
  Series 4. Slides (from accession 2010-021) consists primarily of images of climbs and treks. They are arranged alphabetically.
  - Places, events, and people; arranged chronologically.
    - Alaska with John H., 1966 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Volcanoes, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Cambridge (Mass.), miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Yellowstone, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - IXTA rejects, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Minarets, Indian Rock, Upside Down House, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Waddington, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Berkeley, California brush fire, Tetons, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Spring, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Berkeley, California, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Deni Ester, Fatso Scherezade, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Berkeley, California lab party, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Berkeley, California and Portland, Oregon, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - 1972 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Semyen, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Ruwenzori, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Mount Kenya, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Kili, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Iran, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Shishnag, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 1-2)
    - Kashmir, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 3-4)
    - Kashmir - Tuliyen, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Kashmir, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Kashmir - Kistwak, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 7-9)
    - Noshaq, 1972 (Pakistan?) (Box 22, Folder 10-12)
    - Kabul ( Afganistan), Dehli ( India), Agro [Agra, India?], 1972-1973 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - New Zealand, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 14-16)
    - Nepal, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 17-18)
    - Trisul, 1975: rolls 5-8 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Nepal, 1973: rolls 11-14 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Mt. Baker, May 1973 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Summer, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - North Cascades, July 1973 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Spring, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Pamirs, 1974: rolls 1-5 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Pamirs, 1974: rolls 7-9 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Pamirs, 1974: unnumbered roll (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Pamirs, 1974: unnumbered roll (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Pamirs, 1974: unnumbered roll (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Pamirs N.D. (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Duplicates for Arlene, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - SF, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - 1974 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Trisul, 1975: rolls 1-4 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Trisul, 1975: rolls 5-8 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Trisul, 1975: rolls 9-14 (no roll 12) (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Trisul, 1975: unnumbered rolls (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Trisul, 1975 - 21 Iran 4 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Trisul, 1975: duplicates for Arlene (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Spring, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Fall, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Winter, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - 1975 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Sierras, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Mt. Rainier, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Palisades, September 1976 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - People, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - 1976 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Everest, 1976: Rolls 1,3 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Everest, 1976: Rolls 4-7 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Everest, 1976: Rolls 8-12 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Everest, 1976: Rolls 13-15 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Everest, 1976: Rolls 16-18 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Everest, 1976: Rolls 19-23 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Everest, 1976: Rolls 24-28 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Everest, 1976: Rolls 29-32 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Everest, 1976: Rolls 33-35 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Everest, 1976: Unumbered Rolls (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Nepal, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Good Portraits, 1967-1976 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - 1977 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Joe Rinehart's Everest (too darn), 1977 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Mt. Dana, August 1977 (Vera & Arlene) (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Mt. Ritter, September 1977 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Palisades, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Ecuador, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Ecuador, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Arlene, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Annapurna, 1977 - "Kathmandu & Vicinity", 1976 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Annapurna, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Annapurna, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Arlene & Friends, 1968-1977 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Salt Lake, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - 1978 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - 1978 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - 1978 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Vera & Allison Slides (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Annapurna, 1978: Rolls 1, 2a, 3 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Annapurna, 1978: Rolls 3a-5a (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Annapurna, 1978: Rolls 6a-8a (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Annapurna, 1978: Rolls 8, 9a, 10a (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Annapurna, 1978: Rolls 11a, 12a, 14a (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Annapurna, 1978: Rolls 15, 15a, 16a (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Annapurna, 1978: Rolls 17, 18, 18a (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Annapurna, 1978: Rolls 19, 19a, 20 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Annapurna, 1978: Rolls 20a, 21, 21a (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Annapurna, 1978: Rolls 22, 22a, 23, 24 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Annapurna, 1978: Rolls 25, 26, 26a (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Annapurna, 1978: Rolls 27-29 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Annapurna, 1978: Rolls 31-33 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Annapurna, 1978: Rolls 34-36 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Annapurna, 1978: Rolls 37-39 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Annapurna, 1978: Rolls 40-42 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Annapurna, 1978: Rolls 43-45 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Annapurna, 1978: Rolls 46-48 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Annapurna, 1978: Rolls 49-51 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Annapurna, 1978: Rolls 52-54 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Annapurna, 1978: Rolls 55-58 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Annapurna, 1978: Rolls 59-62 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Annapurna, 1978: Rolls 63-66 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Annapurna, 1978: Rolls 68-71a (no roll 67) (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Annapurna, 1978: Rolls 71-73 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Annapurna, 1978: Rolls 74-76 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Annapurna, 1978: Rolls 77-79 (no roll 78) (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Annapurna, 1978: Duplicates (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Annapurna, 1978: Duplicates (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - 1979 Trek (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - 1979 Unnumbered (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Bhrigupanth (Brigupanth), 1980: Rolls B1-B3 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Bhrigupanth (Brigupanth), 1980: Rolls B5-B7 (no roll B4) (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Bhrigupanth (Brigupanth), 1980: Rolls B8-B10 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Bhrigupanth (Brigupanth), 1980: Rolls B11-B13 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Bhrigupanth (Brigupanth), 1980: Rolls B14-16 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Bhrigupanth (Brigupanth), 1980: Rolls B17-B20 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Bhrigupanth (Brigupanth), 1980: Rolls B21-B23 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Bhrigupanth (Brigupanth), 1980: Rolls B24-B27 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Bhrigupanth (Brigupanth), 1980: Rolls B29-B31 (no roll 28) (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Bhrigupanth (Brigupanth), 1980: Rolls B32-34 (2 roll 33's) (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Bhrigupanth (Brigupanth), 1980: Rolls B35-B38 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Bhrigupanth (Brigupanth), 1980: Rolls B40-B42 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Bhrigupanth (Brigupanth), 1980: Rolls B43-B45 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Bhrigupanth (Brigupanth), 1980: Rolls B46-B48 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Bhrigupanth (Brigupanth), 1980: Rolls B49-B51 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Bhrigupanth (Brigupanth), 1980: Rolls B52-B55 (2 roll 54's, no roll 53) (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Bhrigupanth (Brigupanth), 1980: Rolls B56, B59 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Bhrigupanth (Brigupanth), 1980: Rolls B61, B70 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Bhrigupanth (Brigupanth), 1980: 3 unumbered rolls (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Ladakh, 1980: rolls L1-L3 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Ladakh, 1980: rolls L4-L6 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Ladakh, 1980: rolls L7-L9 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Ladakh, 1980: rolls L10-L12 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Ladakh, 1980: rolls L13-L16 (no roll L14) (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Ladakh, 1980: rolls L17-L19 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Ladakh, 1980: rolls L20-L22 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Ladakh, 1980: rolls L23-L25 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Ladakh, 1980: rolls L26-L28 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Ladakh, 1980: rolls L29-L31 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Ladakh, 1980: rolls L32-L34 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Ladakh, 1980: rolls L35-L37 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Ladakh, 1980: rolls L38-L39 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Ladakh, 1980: rolls L40-L42 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Ladakh, 1980: rolls L43-L45 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Ladakh, 1980: rolls L46-L48 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Ladakh, 1980: rolls L49-L51 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Ladakh, 1980: rolls L52 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Ladakh, 1980: Unnumbered Box 1 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Ladakh, 1980: Unnumbered Box 2 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1981: Bhutan (sheets 1-6, rolls B1-B5) (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1981: Bhutan (sheets 7-12, rolls B5-B9) (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1981: Bhutan (sheets 13-18, rolls B9-B14) (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1981: Bhutan (sheets 19-24, rolls B14-B18,B20) (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1981: Bhutan (sheets 25-30, rolls B20-B25) (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1981: Bhutan (sheets 31-36, B25-B29) (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1981: Bhutan (sheets 37-42, B29-B33) (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1981: Bhutan (sheets 43-48, B33-B38) (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1981: Bhutan (sheets 49-54, B38-B42) (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1981: Bhutan (sheets 55-60, B42-B48) (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1981: Bhutan (sheets 61-66, B48-B53) (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1981: Bhutan (sheets 67-72, B53-B58) (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1981: Bhutan (sheets 73-77, B58-B62) (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1981: Nepal (sheets 1-6, rolls N1-N5) (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1981: Nepal (sheets 7-12, rolls N5-N9) (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1981: Nepal (sheets 13-18, rolls N10-N15) (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1981: Nepal (sheets 19-24, rolls N15-N19) (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1981: Nepal (sheets 25-30, rolls N19-N24) (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1981: Nepal (sheets 31-36, rolls N24-N29) (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1981: Nepal (sheets 37-42, rolls N29-N32) (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1981: Nepal (sheets 43-48, rolls N32-N37) (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1981: Nepal (sheets 49-54, rolls N37-N41) (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1981: Nepal (sheets 55-60, rolls N41-N47) (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1981: Nepal (sheets 61-66, rolls N47,N48,N55,N56,N60,N61) (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1981: Nepal (sheets 67-72, rolls N61, N64-N69) (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1981: Nepal (sheets 73-78, rolls N69-N73,N75) (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1981: Nepal (sheets 79-84, rolls N75-N80) (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1981: Nepal (sheets 85-90, rolls N80-N86) (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1981: Nepal (sheets 91-96, rolls N86,N87,N89-N93) (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1981: Nepal (sheets 97-102, rolls N93-N98) (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1981: Nepal (sheets 103-108, rolls N98-N102) (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1981: Nepal (sheets 109-114, rolls N102-N107) (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1981: Nepal (sheets 115-120, rolls N107-N112) (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1981: Nepal (sheets 121-126, rolls N112-N117) (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1981: Nepal (sheets 127-132, rolls N117-N121) (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1981: Nepal (sheets 133-138, rolls N121-N126) (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1981: Nepal (sheets 139-144, rolls N126-N131) (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1981: Nepal (sheets 145-150, rolls N131-N136) (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1981: Nepal (sheets 151-156, rolls N136-N142) (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1981: Nepal (sheets 157-163, rolls N142-N146) (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1981: Nepal (sheets 164-166,154 - rolls N146-N148) (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1982: East India (sheets 1-8, rolls 1-6) (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1982: India (sheets 1-6, rolls I1-I6) (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1982: India (sheets 7-12, rolls I6,I11-I4) (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1982: India (sheets 13-18, rolls I6,I14-I19) (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1982: India (sheets 19-24, rolls I19-I23) (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1982: India (sheets 25-30, rolls I23-I27) (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1982: India (sheets 31-36, rolls I27-I32) (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1982: India (sheets 37-42, rolls I32-I36) (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1982: India (sheets 43-48, rolls I36-I41) (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1982: India (sheets 49-54, rolls I41-I46) (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1982: India (sheets 55-60, rolls I46-I50) (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1982: India (sheets 61-66, rolls I50-I55) (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1982: India (sheets 67-72, rolls I55-I60) (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1982: India (sheets 73-78, rolls I60-I65) (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1982: India (sheets 79-84, rolls I65-I70) (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1982: India (sheets 85-90, rolls I70-I75) (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1982: India (sheets 91-96, rolls I75-I80) (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1982: India (sheets 97-102, rolls I80-I84) (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1982: India (sheets 103-108, rolls I84-I89) (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1982: India (sheets 109-114, rolls I89-I94) (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1982: India (rolls I95-I97) (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1982: India (rolls I98-I100) (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1982: India (rolls I101-I104) (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1982: India (rolls I105-I107) (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1982: India (rolls I108-I110) (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1982: India (Rolls I111-I113) (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1982: India (Rolls I114-I116) (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1982: India (Rolls I117-I119) (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1982: India (Rolls I120-I122) (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1982: India (Rolls I123-I126) (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1982: India (Rolls I127-I129) (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1982: India (Rolls I130-I132) (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1982: India (Rolls I133-I135) (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1982: India (Rolls I136-I138) (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1982: India (Rolls I139-I142) (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1982: India (Rolls I143-I144) (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous: 1970-1982 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1983: Kathmandu (rolls K1-K3) (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1983: Kathmandu (rolls K4-K6) (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1983: Kathmandu (rolls K7-K9) (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1983: Kathmandu (rolls K10-K12) (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1983: Kathmandu (rolls K13-K15) (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1983: Kathmandu (rolls K16-K18) (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1983: Kathmandu (rolls K19-K21) (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1983: Kathmandu (rolls K22-K24) (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1983: Kathmandu (rolls K25-K27) (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1983: Kathmandu (rolls K28-K30) (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1983: Kathmandu (rolls K31-K32) (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1984: Nepal (rolls N1-N3) (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1984: Nepal (rolls N4-N6) (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1984: Nepal (rolls N7-N9) (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1984: Nepal (rolls N10-N12) (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1984: Nepal (rolls N13-N15) (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1984: Nepal (rolls N16-N18) (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1984: Nepal (rolls N19-N21) (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1984: Nepal (roll N22) (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Great Himalayan Traverse, 1984: India (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Baby in Alps, 1987 (rolls 00-1) (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Baby in Alps, 1987 (rolls 2-5) (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Baby in Alps, 1987 (rolls 6-8) (Box 41, Folder 11)